[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most penguin species are piscivorous, meaning what?", "correct_answer": "They feed primarily on fish", "incorrect_answers": ["They do not drink water", "They have a tubular body shape", "An aquatic animal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do all frogs live their whole life in water?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Biblical characters is known to have the greatest number of children?", "correct_answer": "David", "incorrect_answers": ["Jacob", "King Saul", "Joshua"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How old was Stella Adler when she made her acting debut?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["11", "14", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Shrek wake up the sleeping Princess Fiona when he finds her in the castle surrounded by lava and protected by a fire-breathing dragon in the 2001 movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "He rudely shakes her shouting Wake up!.", "incorrect_answers": ["He kisses her.", "He sets the alarm of his clock.", "He pours a jug of water on her face."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these season do the fruit of the apple tree ripen?", "correct_answer": "Fall", "incorrect_answers": ["Late summer", "Early summer", "Late spring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Moon is changing its position it relation to the Earth. In what way?", "correct_answer": "Moving away", "incorrect_answers": ["Getting closer", "Moving along the Earths Y axis", "Moving along the Earths X axis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Hungarian dish, meaning cowherd, is prepared with beef, onion, red peppers and paprika.", "correct_answer": "Goulash", "incorrect_answers": ["Utopenec", "Bramborak", "Pljeskavica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the missing word in this Irish saying: Every dog is _____ at his own house door.?", "correct_answer": "bold", "incorrect_answers": ["asleep", "lonely", "fearful"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Pursuit of Happyness was released in 2008.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This novel by Ernest Hemingway, set during World War I, is told through the point of view of Lieutenant Frederic Henry who falls in love with nurse Catherine Barkley.", "correct_answer": "A Farewell to Arms", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sun Also Rises", "The Snows of Kilimanjaro", "For Whom the Bell Tolls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the poppy flower symbolize in many cultures as well as in art?", "correct_answer": "Death", "incorrect_answers": ["Sleep", "Oblivion", "All of these"]}]